{
    "id": "fab898787c5548159a0387a309ab44d5",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliaries Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I don’t think that I ………………….. be able to come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "can",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………… not pay unless he is compelled.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "will",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You ..................... be punctual.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "ought"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you ………………….tell me earlier.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "could",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… I help you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Shall",
                "Will",
                "Would"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. you help me with this, please?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Shall",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He said I ………………….. visit him at any time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If you ………………… see her, give her my love.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………….. not ask for a raise for fear of losing his job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dare",
                "need",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. him, so I phoned him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "needn't to see",
                "didn't need to see",
                "needn't have seen"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}